There is another. You have an indian hemp in your pocket.
Come out for deliverance. Jesus Christ will set you free.
After Prophet T.B Joshua had given this prophetic message, this man came out from the crowd and
moved toward the alter in response to the prophesy.
that "there is a man here with indian hemp in his pocket."
As he steps forward to confirm the prophesy, his deliverance is only a moment away
Come here!
Instructing the man to come on the altar, Prophet T.B Joshua reaches into his pocket and pulls out an item.
What is this?
Indian hemp.
Indian hemp?
Watch your screen!
Confirming the prophecy, this is the indian hemp that was inside the mans pocket.
Prophecy Confirmation
Hello sir you are welcome!!
Tell us your name, your state and where you from
My name is Elijah Henry Okechukwu
This is my first time of coming to this place.
I am from Abia State, Nigeria.
We saw that the man of God was calling out words of prophesy during the first service.
You came out in response to one of them. Can you tell us the word of prophesy he spoke to you?
The man of God prophesied that there is a man here with indian hemp.
"Please you should come out!"
There is a brother, you have Indian hemp in your pocket.
Come out for deliverance. Jesus Christ will set you free!!
After Prophet T.B Joshua, have given this prophetic message
This man came from out of the crowd and moved toward the alter in response to the prophesy.
that "there is a man here with indian hemp in his pocket."
As he steps forward to confirm the prophecy, his deliverance is only a moment away.
Come here!
Instructing the man to come unto the alter
Prophet T.B Joshua reaches into his pocket
and pulls out an item.
What is this?
Indian hemp!
Indian hemp.
Watch your screen
Confirming the prophesy, this is the indian hemp that was inside the mans pocket
Immediately he mentioned the case, I became afraid
and something fell on me, so I had to come out...because I am the person.
Since I have been smoking this drug,I have been into a lot of evil...
even bad gangs
You mean that you are the one that the man of God prophesied
that "there is a brother here who has indian hemp in his pocket;
in the house of God, and that mans should come out!."
Yes!
Where is that indian hemp now?
This is the indian hemp.
Okay you mean that this in your hand this is the indian hemp that you brought to the church today
that the man of God prophesied about
Yes!
Have you told anyone that brought indian hemp?
How is it possible, that you think that the man of God could prophesy this?
I am surprised because this drug, I brought it yesterday, I wanted to
smoke it. Later in the night, I fell asleep; so I did not remember.
This morning I said that after the service, I will go out and smoke it
but I was surprised when I came here, the man of God mentioned it.
I became afraid. I have been trying to stop it
but to no avail.
I thank God for being here. I know that since God has
used the man of God to prophesy
about it, I know that the yoke
has been broken in my life.
Amen, continue to yield to the Holy Spirit
and you will be Christ filled, as He continues to lead you
to the throne, thank you!
Amen!